Guide to the John Caughlan Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- John Caughlan papers and photographs, 1936-2003; 0704-003; 2.51 cubic feet 3 boxes
  - PHOTOGRAPHS, 1936-1960s; SERIES VI (Box-folder 3/12-3/23)
    - Court Negatives, Undated (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Professor Herbert Phillips, Undated (Box-folder 3/18)
    - John Caughlan, c. 1940s (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Smith Act Trial/Barry Hatten, c. 1950s (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Washington Commonwealth newsreels, Undated (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Canwell protest, 1948 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Caughlan Family, c. 1960s (Box-folder 3/23)